

DONNA CHOI
UX/UI DESIGNER

PROFILE

I am a UX/UI designer based in the San Francisco Bay Area. I design beautiful & friendly user interfaces and create seamless user experiences. I have a background in Corporate Accounting & Banking, which has taught me to be a problem solver and an effective communicator.

GET IN TOUCH



donnakang713@gmail.com



(408) 482-2213



322 Misty Circle Livermore, CA 94550







WORK EXPERIENCE

Audit Experienced Associate

Jun 2015 - May 2016

PricewaterhouseCoopers LA

- Audited financial statements of public and private companies in the software & tech industry.
- Worked alongside corporate controllers, VPs, and CFOs to complete audits.

Audit Experienced Associate

Sep 2013 - Jun 2015

PricewaterhouseCoopers San Jose

- Conducted interviews with the client to obtain an understanding of their financial data.
- Collaborated with team members to define the project goals and deadlines.

BSA (Bank Secrecy Act) Analyst

May 2011 - Dec 2011

Hanmi Bank

- Analyzed client's financial data for possible money laundering & tax evasions.
- Wrote Suspicious Activity Reports that described potential fraudulent activities in detail.

EDUCATION

SJSU Lucas Graduate School of Business May 2012 – June 2013

Masters of Science in Accountancy

University of California, Davis

Sep 2007 - Dec 2010

• Bachelor of Arts in Economics

Bloc Ux Design Apprenticeship

Nov 2017 - July 2018

• UX Designer Track - Certificate of Completion

SKILLS

- User Experience (UX) Design
- User Interface (UI) Design
- Branding & Identity
- Mobile Design
- User Survey & User Personas
- User Stories & User Flows
- Business Analysis
- Low & High-fidelity Wireframes
- Visual Mockups
- Interactive Prototyping
- Usability Testing
- HTML, CSS, Javascript, and

TOOLKIT













